calling that to order item to his public input in those scheduled personal appearances
and one of the audits that which is to address the council on any of the agenda items.
There have been none out of three is consent agenda staff is recommending items four through nine for the consent agenda.
There are no questions on any of those items at any kind of motion to approve.
I might have to admit that this is a brief part of that add out in the month of June.
Okay? I am 11 being the important team client to the housing authority.
So that the media can't let the media in.
That's right. I can't let them in. So that's all we have to do.
I have a jam.
So I was telling them I was telling them I was going through nine for the consent agenda.
Are there any questions on that we have a motion?
And a second? I guess so.
Call please. Johnson?
All right.
Lewis? I chose.
You only do appreciate the thought.
I didn't attend service bad presentations in Nico.
Miami police department canine officers and I have the badge.
I don't agree.
We want to play Nico up.
We'd like to introduce our new officer.
I'll send you four when we get him as badge.
How pretty do I do?
Do you know what I'm saying?
This is a Nico. He's our new officer. He's been in training for the last seven weeks.
It was just certified by the State of Oklahoma and the taxi.
And we're looking forward to putting the work and having work straight away.
Awesome.
And he'll also be going to the schools as his kids.
Yes, that's all right.
Inside two way to the DHS to a children's first-person fund was I.
My son.
And that was really well with children and hearing his family requested.
I have these schools to help check in that area and I'll sell you them and you won't be
forward to being able to do that.
Are we going to let's just go a little bit along with it?
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Yeah.
All right.
And there's my pleasure.
Nico gave us a little buddy.
I can find a spot in there.
I'm going to have to try and put it.
That's what I'm going to do.
You're going to put it around this.
That's where you want to create a line before.
And you're going to have to let it go.
If I could.
I love employees like this because they're very inexpensive.
I want to be all the city while we have a week off.
We want to give him a gift.
This is a great work site out of it.
Treats.
We're very fortunate to have you.
He was a part of the record by the process.
I was one of those go to us.
We had a large of a nation that was just enormous.
Then chief from the jury tried to match that.
And that's the funds we were able to use to merge the thought.
We wanted to be able to use that because of ourselves.
I think this is the best way we could do that.
I think we're all excited about it.
Being part of the same event.
We're taking our own thing.
That's our 14 months.
Fisher about 15 months.
We're here for the hospital.
Come over to the animal shelter and take sense in our animals.
He's still working on this.
He's so mad.
There we go.
Okay, thanks, Chief.
Thanks officers.
I remember 11 is where we were one of the steep climb.
My name is House of the Dory.
It was termed expired 12321.
I was proposing still to be reported.
Please change your consideration.
We have a motion.
I might come out as part of the virus.
I want to be a comment.
And second.
Second.
And a vote.
Johnson.
Lewis.
I say.
I don't know.
Twelve staff is there for that to be put off for a future meeting.
One or two.
If not, both staff members are sick.
They want to be sure and be here to preserve the information and thought and thoroughly.
And so he asked to put that off.
If we could just have that table to be on the night.
That's a river bus.
Okay.
So we'll take one.
Twelve.
Item 13 is also a consent agenda.
Listing a lot of items that are all ordinance updates.
And then you just kind of give us an overview of what this is.
You're being whoever or not.
But what this is about.
Yeah, I'd be more than happy to.
These are the ordinances that were presented at a work session.
A couple of months ago.
Basically what was asked is what the state question 780 and 781 being passed at the election a year ago.
The which made some significant changes to the law in the state of Oklahoma.
We were needing to make a number of changes to our ordinances.
we were in compliance with the provisions of the law.
And so it's resulted in these,
I mean, here we have eight different ordinance changes.
Now, two of them are actually separate from 780,
but they're in philosophically, they're along the same lines
of what was addressed in state question 780,
and so we thought it would be a good time
to go ahead and take care of those two.
But basically, these are, to bring our ordinances
on receiving stolen property, on possession of marijuana.
That is a specific ordinance that we had,
we're changing it in conformity with 780 to cover
all of the illegal drugs, making those a misdemeanor charge,
so that they could be, could be, don't have to be,
but they could be prosecuted in city court,
if that is the termination made by the prosecuting attorney.
We also have the, we're changing our general punishment
ordinance to bring it into compliance with what the law otherwise provides.
And our idea, the follow-up idea of that was to get our punishment
to where it does not carry jail time, but the punishment is up to $500.
If there is not any other specific punishment set out in a specific ordinance.
And that threshold of $500 is important because it intrigues other rights,
I guess, would be the only way to say it, but other right consequences.
Correct.
And then it also includes a gesting our varsity ordinance,
our bogus check ordinance, defrauding in-keepers,
and that's one of the new ones that we have, and although it's called defrauding in-keepers,
it also covers the circumstance where somebody, for instance, walks their ticket at a restaurant.
Shoplifting, and then it's called the gasoline pump theory,
which is a drive-off from the gas station.
So do you see these, is this the list in Tolerary,
they bring more to us later, or is pretty much taken care of it?
We have other ordinances that we're working on, but these are all of the ones that were related
to state question, 780.
Sorry.
So, Ben, thanks for that explanation.
Do we have a motion to approve item?
11.
Yes.
And a second?
Local police.
Johnson.
Lewis.
I.
Weston.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Just for the record that should be item 13.
Or am.
Let me buy it up.
And see where I'm on.
So do you have most to approve out of 13 also?
That's.
Yeah.
It was item 13.
And I'll still second.
And.
I.
Thank you.
So then.
That.
Just.
I don't.
14.
Did you want us to go around that?
I was going to suggest that.
We have a relative.
We're right agenda.
That possibly.
We might do this at the very end.
I know we do have one.
Executive session.
It's really shouldn't last that long.
But the thinking that we could do the PowerPoint.
And then.
From that point.
We could take the tour and from there.
Pretty much a journal.
As we finished the tour.
And that way we would have come back here in Germany.
You basically.
So are you wanting to.
Executive session right now.
Well, we could go.
We could finish up this agenda.
Okay.
And then we could.
Coming to the executive session.
And then what I was.
I think what I was looking to say is.
Resets the meeting.
And take the tour.
And then adjourn whatever we've finished the tour.
And then is there any reason why we.
Can we adjourn in a different location.
Or do we need to be here to adjourn.
That's an interesting question.
I don't think that we.
No, no, we need.
The agenda says we're meeting here.
Okay.
So what is.
We'll.
Yes.
So we're going to pass a lot of 14 for now.
And 15 is new business.
Any new business.
Dean.
Doctor.
Staff reports.
Any new packet.
Mayor and council committee announcements.
Neil.
And something you want to say.
I'm sure.
I just want to.
Right.
I was the.
The.
I think it's appropriate.
And I do think that I wanted to have that.
have came together for an event for the entire community, it's really very impressive, you know.
Yeah, nothing but price, even people from the defendants that came here, very, very impressive what we were able to do.
would be here in my hand and for those, a lot of good queues for that, yeah.
A couple of other things, this is a very important reminder on December 13th at 630
at the Colenvolver. The Federal Energy Regulatory Commission will occur is going to be having
an informational meeting regarding the real licensing of the Pensacola Dam and GRDF.
And this goes right to the heart of how the dam and the lake is operated.
And it's about a five-year period of time, this process checks.
And once that license is in place, that license would be in place for probably over 25 years.
So this is a very crucial and critical process that we are going to be involved in.
And I hope that I know that the paper already had a great article about this coming up,
and we will be putting notifications on our Facebook page.
But we hope that everybody will listen to this,
that you will be able to attend that meeting,
and listen to what this process is about.
So it's the most important thing.
The energy is going to be on December 13th, that is Wednesday, starting in 630 pm,
and it's going to be held in the Colenvolver.
That is a public meeting. Everybody is welcome to attend.
And encourage to attend.
We really need a good turnout.
We need to.
Fark needs to.
We need to demonstrate to Fark how important this is to our community.
And a big turnout is a good way to do that.
And I will tell you that, for originally started, which was three meetings.
There were two at the Langley Center for GRDA and one at the Grove City Hall.
And basically a post that was said, this is critical.
From Miami, they agreed that a fourth meeting would appreciate that.
The final thing I want to bring up is our December 19th meeting.
We're talking about trying to see if we might be able to have a different time for that meeting.
I think we have some people that have some conflicts in the evening.
And we're wondering if possibly we still have a meeting on a 19th, instead of meeting at 530,
costs will be meeting at about 3 or 330.
They're thinking, what do you want to say this?
We're not sure what your schedule is like that day.
How are you not?
You're wondering.
So, I think possibly we have some potential ordinances for our cemetery.
The rolloff prep, of course, we want to bring back to you.
And then that grace will be clear for the discussion about the R's class.
So, as I said, I think what all the aspects and so do you try to make the decision now.
Why do I have asthma, listen to get with you to look at that time?
And as I said, we've become a special meeting with darkness.
So, maybe that doesn't have to be that one.
Maybe we might do it earlier in the week or later in the week.
All right. So that's it. That's it. Thank you.
Thank you. So item 19 and executive session,
percent of the 25LS subsection 307 before.
And so we have most you go to executive session
upon my recommendation. I'm just going to.
Our city attorney's recommendation.
Yes. Okay.
Second.
Go Paul.
Johnson.
Okay.
And then.
Johnson.
I chose.
This again, it's in the amount of 567-13.
So we're now going to go back to item 14,
which is Civic Center. We have in Jim project
in two. We're going to start with a.
How do you point?
Okay.
I don't know.
Wait. Okay.
So if you want to take that table up there.
Back in Jim, you have a council.
Approved your budget. And within that budget,
you approve to use $2.4 million out of our any day fund
for facilities improvements.
$2.8 million and $8,290 of that.
$2.4 is for the Civic Center.
Okay.
And that also includes our architectural fees.
You can also see where we spent 17,000
on the color theater.
The paint.
The exterior.
So that means about to $2.93.
$7.81 for facilities improvements.
Just kind of giving them to people right now.
And Jeremy's going to talk.
So are we.
Is this $2.89,000?
Is that a big number?
This is a farm number now.
The gross maximum price.
$1.954.367.
And then if you add in GH2's,
$1.304,000,
if you want that.
$2.89,000.
Okay. So any increases or any
expenditures of that $2.903,000.
We'll come back before the council.
Okay.
And within that $2,000.
is our contingency and he'll talk about that.
Correct.
All right.
Hi, John.
John, we held a cross in the structure.
This is my capital.
Cross in the structure.
If you go on to the next slide.
We're here to talk about the project going on in the city hall and the regroup.
As Jill said, that's our GMB for the project.
Not including GH2 and our technical fees.
Our initial built-in contingency was 85,643 police.
And now let's build on the project and create the project.
It's 719,000 percent complete on this project.
We're at 60 percent.
We're going to finish a bit in the February.
Go the next slide.
Wow.
This is the GMB that was presented by John and July.
You can see this.
So, Jill, this won't do that.
That is every every scope of every line I'm on.
The project and the contract amounts and shows all our.
All our.
All the contingency's fillers at risk, you know.
GMB all that.
Okay.
So, the next slide.
And the contingency is still unspanned at this point.
That's the first step.
Some.
We're going to go for it.
Okay.
This is.
So, what I'm going to go through the next key slide right now.
Tell you what we've spent in contingency.
So, our architectural, something on the right side of the one.
What they're called.
We're going to go through changes.
And in the area over here in open office area, we did some changes.
We we have a block wall that we thought hey, we could take this out.
And put it some not open the space up a little bit more.
Added some outlets and bad.
It was a big change.
But it was a change to the better token of this ring.
We spent 26.777 on that.
Okay.
Next slide.
Say a slide.
Thank you.
Today we will go through the next slide.
Yes.
Next slide.
As I told you, we did a pretty good change.
In the correm area, in the council room.
Kind of a little twist, of how the.
The DIA is going to serve sit there and we did a little twist.
There are just some column changes.
Add some.
But we spent nine hours on that change.
But we'll get to see that in a minute.
And we go to the segway.
You can see the things we want to explain to you.
But, go.
Next slide.
Councilor Roon, we had some lights, some switches, some data, about $4,99, or $6,000, $6,000.
Those are the three ASIs, our picture of some of the own instructions that we have approved
two date that have been presented in our own part of the story.
And taking out of the contingency, go to the next slide.
Also part of the contingency of the length of we had spent where we were some request
and some RFIs that we sent into GH2.
And what this is, is we have additional steel.
review of them in the office area, folks have dedicated out doors to them, which is called
a do-as, which is going to, it's part of your HAC system. This, this has to be supported,
and we'll see this here a minute at the roof line, and supporting anything in it, this
has fell on the roof. We spent $7,000 in here for the dollar from that. Next slide, we'll
send you. We added some door hardware on my door, or to the bank of the range, and that cost
$2,200 and $2,200 in the next slide. Those are all the money that we spent for the
content you see. When you do have a couple other changes that are possibilities that will
kind of, and we're pricing these right now to firm these numbers up, we're going to do a window
change, it kind of helps us obtain a warranty for the roof over on the north portion of the roof
that we're working on. We're going to try and put some metal panels in open-ups in glass so we can put
our roofing and then bring up so high to get obtained a warranty. Now this is the window at the
stair. Yes, there's a stair. We're still working on trying to get a resolution that is easier for the elevator.
That's just a gas donation. The darker the engineer and the columns of electric and us,
we're working on trying to get that result. Those are the only money that we see that we have come
up on the horizon. You do have an ASI for that that is kind of encapsulating those two items. So
the next slide. Here's the breakdown of the continuity, so this is plain as it gets. That's what we
got left to spend for the project before we would ever have a true change order on this project.
They would increase the NP. That's what they last slide. That's the NP.
So they may have any questions. Oh, we'll just name this circle. We'll go this way. Yeah, we'll go that way.
So February 28 is for Jack and conclusion date.
Wow, that's cool. What this. Creator. Real quick on that elevator. What that booster is,
when we were switching over to the new 208 electrical panel, we had the O240, which is the big
transformer's outside the PD. The 208 is the pad now. When we switched that over to the 208, the
elevator would not function. Even though we were running at 213, the NP would not function. So we had to put it back
on the 240, and we called it in, cone-A, which is our elevator happening, and we couldn't find that,
it has to be a turn of 40 volts. So we have to boost that to the late back to 240 to get the elevator
function. It is fully functional now, but it's just still on the old panel. In the 88 hardware,
he was talking about, we had all the upgrades to the sidewalks, the staircases, and somewhere in that
process, we left out the push button.
on my door. So that's where that is coming in as so. So what have been part of the original scope?
What have you done? It was just an overstock.
Get correct.
All right.
Let's see.
I'm sorry.
That was just how to make the best.
This thing is a second.
This is a second.
So we have next year brothers.
I need to talk about that.
I need to talk about it.
So this is a second.
One.
What will be the next?
We are running off.
You have a lot of things to sign.
It will be next.
Okay.
We are going to do this.
I don't think we are trying to do it.
We are not trying to do it.
So Neil has made a motion to adjourn.
I'll second it.
Roll call.
Johnson.
This time.